I just spent an unforgettable 14 days
traveling through South Korea.
The aim of this trip was to experience the
very best the country had to offer.
From the vibrant and busy
capital of Seoul,
to the coastal charms of Busan
with its sandy
beaches and lively markets.
And finally, Jeju Island, known for its
breathtaking natural scenery.
If you're planning to do a similar trip,
or in search of some inspiration,
then join
me on this incredible journey through
the heart of South Korea.
Here's how to spend 14 days
in South Korea.
Here's a quick overview of the trip.
We'll begin with 6 days in Seoul, diving
into the heart of the capital.
Exploring its dynamic districts
like Myeongdong,
Hongdae, and Gangnam,
visiting iconic landmarks
such as Gyeongbokgung Palace
and N Seoul Tower
while indulging in its vibrant
culinary scene.
Next, we head south to Busan.
We take in the coastal scenery and stroll
along the sandy beaches of
Haeundae and Gwangalli.
We visit a cliffside temple
and wander through a
historic village and explore
the busy markets.
And finally, we wrap things up
on Jeju island,
renting a car and setting
off on a scenic
drive around its lush landscapes.
From waterfalls to volcanic craters,
we discover the island's natural
wonders at our own pace,
enjoying a slower rhythm of travel.
Before we begin, let's get the
basics out of the way.
The best season to visit South Korea is
either autumn or spring, as
the weather conditions
are milder during this time.
We want to avoid the summer months since
the country is notorious for
its hot and humid weather
Winter can be an option to avoid the crowds,
but the temperatures can be freezing.
South Korea boasts an extensive public
transportation system, making it
simple to navigate through
the entire country.
During our journey, we'll mostly use a
combination of trains and buses
to get in and around the cities
For this, the T-Money Travel Card will
be our key to the country.
It works similarly to other rechargeable
transportation cards.
It can even be used as a payment form at
selected stores and vending machines.
During our time in Korea, we also
frequently use local taxis.
Taxis in South Korea are relatively
affordable.
We mostly use them when traveling
with large luggage.
To get a hold on one, we use
the Kakao Taxi app.
It's fairly simple to use and
especially useful
if you don't speak Korean,
since you can input
the destination even before
entering the taxi,
saving yourself from some
embarrassing attempts
at speaking your broken Korean.
Getting around on foot, we
used a Naver map.
It's similar to Google Maps, which
unfortunately doesn't currently
offer walking directions
in Korea, but it does still show
you your live GPS location.
Naver Map has an English
interface, but it
can still be tricky at times
to find specific
locations as the English translations of
place names can be a bit hit and miss.
My solution was to switch between
Naver Map and Google Maps.
I found it easier to search for locations in
Google Maps first, then copy the place
name or address in Korean and paste it
into Naver Map to get directions.
Here's a list of some essential apps
you should consider using.
The already mentioned Naver Map
for navigation.
Papago, a handy translation
app you can use
to communicate with locals
or translate food
menus or signs in Korean.
Kakao Taxi, the best app to use when
you need to get a taxi.
And CatchTable, a popular
dining reservation
app that allows you to make
reservations at
many popular restaurants in South Korea.
If you want a written version
of all of this,
then I'm glad to announce
my 14 days in South Korea
travel guide is now available.
This plus 280 page guide
is based on my own
journey through South Korea
covering Seoul,
Busan and Jeju Island.
Inside you'll find detailed
insights on where
to stay, how to get around,
your travel budget
and much more.
I've included over 200 hand-picked
recommendations
covering activities,
restaurants,
and cafes,
many of which aren't mentioned
in this video.
And best of all, each one comes with a
Naver Map link to make navigation
as easy as possible.
I spent weeks putting this
guide together to
make it the most helpful
resource for anyone
planning a trip to South Korea.
So if that's you, then consider
checking it out.
The guide is now available
on my personal store.
We begin in Seoul, a sprawling metropolis
where ancient temples stand
in the shadows
of large skyscrapers.
This city is a collision of past,
present, and future,
a place where tradition and innovation
come together
to create a dynamic cultural hub.
We arrive in Seoul and stay in the
popular area of Myeongdong.
This area is famous for its shopping,
Korean skincare,
cosmetics, and its many street
food stalls.
Given its commercial appeal
and central location,
Myeongdong is arguably the
best place to stay
for first-time visitors.
We opted to stay at the Lotte Hotel
due to its prime location,
which was located right next to
the main shopping area
of Myeongdong.
On our first full day in Seoul,
we kick things off with Itaewon.
But first, a visit to the
iconic N Seoul Tower,
also known as Namsan Tower.
For 40 years, this towering
landmark has stood
as a symbol of Korea and a key
tourist attraction in the city.
To get up to the tower, most folks
take the cable car,
which is a quick and easy ride.
If you're feeling adventurous,
you could decide to hike up,
which takes around 30 to 40 minutes.
Just brace yourself for a lot of stairs.
You'll also find hundreds,
if not thousands,
of love locks near the tower.
Before leaving, we also decided
to participate
and bought our very own lock.
We head down to Itaewon and
visit Rain Report,
a weather-themed cafe.
The cafe serves up a variety of
beverages and desserts
in a sleek, modern setting.
The interior is dominated by
black design elements
and multiple screens displaying
rain scenes
and weather forecast, creating a
newsroom-like atmosphere.
And outside, you'll find a line of people
gathering around to snap photos
of the artificial rainfall display,
which happens every 15 minutes.
As for some personal favorites,
the sesame latte is a must-try,
and a black cloud cake was
a dessert to die for.
Post-coffee break, we make our way
to the Leeum Museum of Art.
This museum is celebrated for its mix
of traditional Korean and
contemporary art.
It comprises three distinct buildings,
one for traditional Korean art,
one for modern works,
and a third dedicated to children's
education.
For dinner, we dive headfirst
into Korean barbecue
at the Maple Tree House.
This Korean barbecue restaurant
offers a solid selection of meats
with an upscale, yet cozy atmosphere.
Just order the classics and pair them
with a couple of beers
for a quintessential Korean
barbecue experience.
Afterwards, we make our way
back to Myeongdong,
where the streets are busy and lined up
with street food stalls as far
as the eye can see.
You can either opt for browsing
the many Korean skincare
stores in the area,
or if you've got a little more
room for a snack,
then hit up the street food stalls.
There's no shortage of tasty and
creative snacks to try.
Looking for more things to do?
Then here's a short list.
On day two, we spend the entire
day exploring Hongdae,
named after the nearby Hongik University.
The area serves as a cultural
entertainment hub,
especially popular among students
and young adults.
You'll find plenty of affordable
trendy fashion shops,
diverse street food offerings, and
live street performances.
First, we visit this unique urban park
that offers a refreshing green space
amidst the bustling city.
It follows the path of a railway line,
transforming what was once a railroad
into a vibrant linear park.
Next, we explore the main shopping
street of Hongdae.
You'll find plenty of clothing
stores to explore,
street food to sample,
and even a shooting range
if you're up for testing your skills.
However, arguably the main attraction
of the area,
aside from shopping, is the live
street performances.
At any given moment, the
street comes alive
as performers showcase everything
from magic tricks
to high energy K-pop dance shows.
There is never a dull moment in Hongdae.
Next, we make a visit to Acorn Caricature.
Here you'll find a friendly artist
who will draw a cute caricature
of you on a canvas.
It's a quirky heartfelt souvenir
that perfectly captures the spirit
of our time in Hongdae.
If photos are more your thing,
then head to this unique photo booth
called Don't Look Up.
It's a photo booth that
allows you to take
some interesting images
from a unique top-down perspective.
For a coffee break,
we head to the cafe
called Shin Lee Doga,
a picturesque cafe located inside
a renovated hanok.
Whether you choose to sit inside
or in the open courtyard,
it's a delightful spot to relax,
take a breather,
or perhaps snap a few pictures.
If you're a big Ghibli fan,
then perhaps you would rather want
to visit the Koriko Cafe,
a charming and whimsical cafe
themed after the beloved Studio
Ghibli animated film
Kiki's Delivery Service.
If you're a fan of the film
or any Ghibli movie,
then this is a must-visit.
The cafe offers beverages and pastries
inspired by the film, such as
this iced Americano.
There's also a small souvenir
shop on the ground floor
selling official Studio Ghibli
merchandise.
If you're hungry, then I recommend
stopping by
Oreno Ramen, a Michelin-awarded
ramen shop.
Get the restaurant's signature
Tori Paitan ramen.
It's a bowl of noodles with a deeply rich
and flavorful creamy chicken base.
It's honestly one of the best
ramens I've ever tried,
so I highly recommend swinging
by if you got the chance.
Very good.
I'm surprised.
Usually you think ramen, you think Japan,
but I honestly think they do
pretty decent effort here.
It's really good.
For more things to do in Hongdae,
consider the following.
On day three, we visit the
Bukchon Hanok Village.
A charming historic district
known for its well-preserved traditional
Korean houses,
also known as Hanok's, which dates
back to the Joseon Dynasty.
Wandering through the narrow
and winding alleyways
of the Hanok Village, visitors
can experience
a slice of Korea's past.
Many of the beautifully restored Hanok's
now serve as accommodations,
cafes, tea houses,
and small workshops.
We make a quick stop at a
New Balance sneaker shop,
which is located inside yet another
beautifully restored Hanok.
After browsing a few items,
I decided to pick up a new pair of shoes.
After some exploring, it's
time for a break
to stay in tune with the ongoing
Hanok theme.
We visit Onion Cafe, a popular cafe
housed in a renovated Hanok.
The cafe features an impressive
selection of pastries
and baked goods all made in-house.
We decided to pick up a couple
of interesting items
along with their signature goods.
How is it?
Good. Sweet.
After refueling, we make our way
to Gyeongbokgung Palace,
one of South Korea's most iconic
and historically significant landmarks.
Built in 1395 during the Joseon Dynasty,
it served as the main royal palace.
The palace complex is vast.
Showcasing traditional Korean
architecture,
about one third of the original
500 buildings
have been restored, though many were lost
or damaged during times of war.
We were lucky enough to experience
the palace after dark,
which gave it an almost magical
and mysterious vibe.
The night event is usually held
for a limited time during
spring and autumn,
so make sure the purchase
your tickets in advance
if you're interested in visiting.
In the evening, I highly recommend
strolling through the Hanok village
once the crowds have thinned out.
Looking for more things to do,
here's a short list.
On day four, we head to Gangnam.
But before that, grab some
morning noodles
at the famous Myeongdong Kyoja.
It's so stable since 1966,
Myeongdong Kyoja
is famous for its hand-cut
kalguksu noodles
served in a rich chicken broth.
Do also make sure to order a round
of their signature dumplings.
After a satisfying meal,
we head to Gangnam
and start the day at the
Bonguensa Temple.
The temple itself has undergone
numerous renovations
and reconstructions over the centuries.
It's known for being a beautiful
and quiet sanctuary,
amidst Seoul's busy Gangnam district.
The highlight of the temple
is the tall statue
of the future Buddha, one of the
tallest stone statues
in the country.
Next, we head to COEX Mall
and visit the Starfield Library.
Known for its design featuring
towering bookshelves
that reach up to 13 meters,
the library houses approximately
50,000 books
and 600 types of magazines,
with numerous seating areas,
from cozy nooks to communal tables.
However, most tourists come
here for the photos
by the escalator.
You'll find plenty of shopping
opportunities at COEX,
as well as the COEX Aquarium,
which we also decided to visit.
This impressive indoor oceanic world
is home to over 40,000 marine creatures
across roughly 650 species,
displayed in 14 themed zones.
Next, we head to Apgujeong,
an upscale neighborhood filled
with flagship stores,
designer boutiques, and luxury brands.
Here are a few of the stores we visited.
Ader Eror, a streetwear brand
with a cult following.
Blends bold designs with playful
deconstructed aesthetics.
Its flagship store in Apgujeong
is a visual treat
and is more like an art exhibition
than a retail store.
It's worth coming by,
even if you don't plan to
do any shopping.
Tambourines is a Korean fragrance brand
known for its minimalist aesthetics
and artistic approach to scent.
Blending high-quality ingredients
with innovative design,
the brand creates unique perfumes
and hand-care products.
Gentle Monster is a Korean eyewear brand
celebrated for its bold designs and
immersive retail spaces.
InstantFunk is a Seoul-borne unisex,
casual fashion label,
defined by its playful mix
of vintage nostalgia
and contemporary cool.
Worksout is a high-end streetwear
retailer,
housed in a striking, three-story
building,
it offers an expansive gallery-like space
filled with over 40 curated brands.
Located in the trendy Do San Park area,
Nudake offers a unique fusion of art
and culinary innovation.
As a concept cafe by Gentle Monster,
it specializes in pastries
that look almost too stunning to eat.
Each dessert is a creative experiment,
pushing the boundaries of what cakes
and pastries can be.
As evening arrives, we make our
final stop of the day
at the Banpo Bridge for the
Rainbow Fountain Show.
Known as the longest bridge
fountain in the world,
equipped with over 200 LED lights,
the fountain creates a vibrant,
colorful water display
synchronized with music.
The shows run multiple times a day,
with each display lasting
around 20 minutes.
You'll also find many food
stalls by the bridge,
so it's the perfect place to hang out,
grab a snack, while enjoying the scenery.
On our fifth day, we head to Ikseongdong,
a charming Hanok village.
The morning started off with rain, which did
give the area an interesting vibe.
However, the weather quickly dried up.
This charming labyrinth of narrow alleyways
is a delightful mix of old and new.
Traditional Hanok houses reimagine as
small boutiques, cozy tea houses,
and aesthetic cafes
It's a kind of place where you can lose
track of time simply by wandering
around and
soaking in the atmosphere.
As for a cafe recommendation,
one stand-out
is Cheongsudang, a beautiful
Hanok style cafe
with a garden theme that almost feels like
stepping into a Studio Ghibli film.
Their most popular items
are the traditional
yakwa desserts,
and their made
to order souffle castella cake
For a different option, consider visiting the
Soha Salt Pond Cafe,
known for its unique
salt-infused baked goods.
Their signature saltbread,
a soft and fluffy
bun with a subtle salty sweetness,
has become a local favorite.
Next, we walk down to
the Cheongyecheon stream,
an 11-kilometer-long
restored waterway that
flows through the heart of the city.
This urban waterway is a testament to
Seoul's dedication to green spaces.
Even spot fish darting through
the water and
and hop across stepping stones
that connect the
two sides of the stream.
As we follow along the stream,
we eventually
reach Gwangjang Market, one
of Seoul's oldest
and largest traditional markets.
It's the perfect place to dive into the
vibrant culinary world of South Korea.
The market is lined with food stalls and
restaurants dishing out every
imaginable Korean food.
Lisa decided to try some
mung bean pancakes,
a crispy Korean savory pancake
made from ground
mung beans and vegetables.
Mung bean pancakes
How is it?
Do you like it?
We also decided to try these fish-shaped
cakes that comes with
different fillings
like red bean paste and custard cream.
We also couldn't resist the
kalguksu
from the renowned knife cut noodle
lady of Netflix fame,
an unmissable experience
for any food enthusiast.
Observing her as she expertly
hand cuts the
noodles for each bowl is
just as memorable
as tasting it.
When a bowl comes scorching
hot, the broth
is clear, rich in umami,
and the noodles are
thick and chewy.
It's really hot.
It's okay.
The noodles are really thick.
Nowadays it's a very popular place, but I
would say it's still worth
experiencing if
you're anywhere near Gwangjang Market.
Next we make our way to
Dongdaemun Design Plaza.
Dongdaemun Design Plaza,
also known as DDP,
is a multicultural complex
and architectural landmark.
It stands out for its futuristic design
and multi-functional space.
The complex supports and
spreads the culture
and development of design
and fashion in South Korea.
It hosts various cultural
events, including
exhibitions, fashion shows,
and conferences.
Not far from DDP, you'll
find the DOOTA Mall,
which beckons with its eight
floors of fashion
and brand stores.
Open until midnight is the
perfect place for
those late night shopping urges,
whether you're
hunting for latest trends or just want to
indulge in some retail therapy.
For dinner, we return to Ikseongdong
for a dinner reservation
at Oncheonjip, a
shabu-shabu restaurant
housed in a restored hanok with a small
open courtyard in the center.
We ordered the Korean beef set for two
and found the meal delicious.
I personally enjoy these
cook-it-yourself experiences
as they remind me of dining
at home with the family.
For more things to do around the
area, here's a short list.
For our final day in Seoul,
we spend the day in Seongsu,
a vibrant up-and-coming
neighborhood in Seoul.
Often referred to as the
Brooklyn of Seoul,
Seongsu has transformed from a
primarily industrial area
into a trendy artistic district,
blending its industrial heritage
with modern and artistic flair.
Our day kicks off with a
bagel pilgrimage to
to Kokkili Bagel,
also known as Elephant Bagel.
This two-store gem is a haven
for bagel lovers.
On the ground floor, you can watch
the staff whip up an impressive
array of bagels, while the second floor
offers plenty of seating spots.
Whether you're in the mood for a classic
or something more adventurous,
there's a bagel here
to match your craving.
Seongsu is a treasure trove
of unique shopping experiences.
Here are the following standouts.
Standoil is a contemporary bag brand,
known for its sleek designs
and everyday versatility.
The ADER ERROR store in Seongsu is an
extension of the band's creative universe.
Designed with ADER ERROR
signature aesthetics
the store blurs the line
between fashion and art.
BALBAL Vintage is a hidden gem for those
who love timeless fashion with character.
With a mix of rare finds and classic pieces
the store offers a unique selection of vintage
clothing and accessories.
EQL is a fashion concept store that
brings together emerging designers,
streetwear, and contemporary trends,
in a carefully curated space.
The Dior store in Seongsu is a striking
blend of luxury and innovation.
Housed in a modern
architectural masterpiece
the space reinterprets the brand's
timeless elegance
with a contemporary edge.
For a quick coffee break,
we visit OUDE Bakery.
This minimalist bakery cafe housed in a
standalone factory building is
renown for its delectable
pastries which have become a favorite
among visitors.
Next we arrive at the Seoul Forest Park.
This sprawling green space was once a
water treatment facility now
transformed into a
multi-purpose urban park.
The park features lush walking paths,
bike rentals, flower gardens,
wildlife you can feed,
and interactive art installations.
Overall, it's a place that is both popular
amongst families
and couples.
For our final meal in Seoul,
we head to Mongtan.
Located in the back streets of Yongsan.
Mongtan has earned a cult following
with expertly grilled meats.
The restaurant is best known
for its boneless short ribs
that undergoes a dry aging process,
then first seared over
traditional straw fire,
with the ribs then
brought to the table
and grilled further
on a hot iron lid.
Your bite is rich, smoky, and
deeply satisfying.
Every meal is then finished off with
the optional kimchi fried rice.
Overall, an elevated take on Korean
barbecue that still feels grounded
in tradition.
If you're looking for
something different to do
then consider doing some hiking in
Bukhansan National Park,
for example, the hike to Baegundae Peak.
If hiking isn't your thing, then here
are some different options.
As our time in Seoul ends, we make the
journey down south to Busan.
Our journey to Busan starts
from Seoul Station.
We decided to take the KTX
train to Busan.
From Seoul, it takes a little over
2 hours to reach Busan.
These areas are arguably the best place
to stay while exploring Busan.
The first being Seomyeon.
Seomyeon is a busy downtown area,
mostly known for its shopping,
food, and nightlife.
Thanks to its central location,
it's arguably the best place to stay
if you intend to explore the whole city.
Next is Haeundae.
Haeundae is Busan's
most famous beach.
Here you'll find 5-star hotels,
soft sand, ocean views,
and a lively atmosphere.
It's a little further out, so you do need
to factor in some travel time,
but it's an excellent place to relax,
and get that essential
Busan beach experience.
Next to Haeundae,
you'll find Gwangalli.
Gwangalli is a popular seaside area,
especially amongst locals.
Famous for its stunning views
of the Gwangan bridge,
it's less crowded than Haeundae
but just as pretty and full of life.
It's slightly closer to the central part
of the city, but not by much.
And finally, we have Nampo.
Nampo-dong is the old
downtown area of Busan.
Here you'll find many traditional markets
street food,
and of course, the famous
Jagalchi fish market.
It's the place to stay if you want to
experience a bit of the old side of Busan.
For our time in Busan,
we decided to stay in Gwangalli.
We stayed at this lovely accommodation
which provided an amazing view
of the nearby bridge.
The place had more than enough room for
the both of us, and can easily
fit a group of people.
The space overall was tastefully
decorated,
it featured a bath in the living space,
and a fully functioning kitchen.
We really enjoyed staying in, just
relaxing and taking in the beautiful
night view of
the lit up Gwangan bridge.
On our first day in Busan,
we head to Nampo-dong
and visited the famous
Jagalchi market,
one of Korea's largest and
most famous seafood markets.
Jagalchi is regarded as the beating heart
of the city's seafood scene
walkng through the market
you're enveloped in a sensory
overload of sights, sounds, and smells.
This isn't simply just a market,
it's a testament to
the city's resilience
and deep connection to the sea
Alright, so we are in Jagalchi market
we just spent half an hour walking around
downstairs where you see all these
different fish vendors.
And then after just checking things out,
we started upstairs where you can find
the restaurants and this is where you
can just go in and order
through like a normal menu basically.
But you could also go downstairs and buy
the fish and then bring it up and have
these different restaurants cook it for you.
Now if you do that, obviously
it costs a little bit extra
to prepare the food, etc.
But if you don't know what you want and
you don't know like how the fish is going
to come out, I recommend just going up to
the second floor, that's
where all the restaurants are.
You see a menu, you can
pick out what you want.
It's a little bit cheaper, but of course
you don't get that experience of picking
the individual fish or
shellfish that you want.
But me and Lisa just decided to head up
and just look at the menu and pick out
whatever we felt like.
We just want to taste a little bit of
everything, a little bit of
clams, a little bit of fish.
Lisa's been dying to try
a seafood pancake
so let's check it out.
Is it worth it?
Yes.
We also ordered some sashimi
and a couple of shellfish.
Oh yeah, oh yeah.
After Jagalchi, we made our way to
nearby Biff Square, the beating
heart of the Busan
International Film Festival.
Named in 1996, this area isn't just about
cinema, it's also a street food haven.
The streets are lined with
vendors offering
every kind of Korean street
food imaginable.
As we ventured deeper into the old town,
we found ourselves at Gukje Market.
Gukje means international and was set up
by post-Korean war refugees
selling smuggled
and imported goods which laid the foundations
for the current Gukje Market.
You find everything from street food,
machinery tools to kitchenware.
Not far from Gukje, we make our
way to the Busan Tower.
Built in 1973, as a symbol for Busan's
future development and prosperity,
the tower rises
120 meters above the nearby park.
Here you'll find locals engaging in
games of Korean chess and go.
For dinner, we decided to get some pizza
near our accommodations
and visited the Sol Tap House.
It was great to have
a little break from
all the Korean food,
and the pizzas here
were honestly great.
They were so good that we
actually ordered
takeaway on one of the separate
nights here.
After dinner, we head
down to Gwangalli beach
and find this very interesting,
slow mailbox.
Essentially, you can write a letter and
have it arrive in about a year's time.
I found it to be a quirky little activity
and it was free of charge,
so why not write one?
Afterwards we spent the rest of the
evening enjoying the view of
the Gwanggan Bridge.
Both from the beach and from
our accommodation.
For more things to do, check
out the following.
For our second day in Busan,
We booked tickets for the
Haeundae Blueline Sky Capsules.
This 30 minute journey,
drifting from Mipo
to Cheongsapo and about 10
meters above the ground
offers views of the ocean
and the coastal landscapes.
It's the type of unique experience that
makes you fall in love with Busan.
We get off at the Cheongsapo station and make
our way to the nearby observatory.
However it was too windy when we were there
so they had to close off access to it.
We continued by strolling
along the coastal
road until we found ourselves
at this seafood restaurant
We ordered a set of abalone
ramyun, a dish
that perfectly marries the
briny freshness
of the sea with the comforting warmth
of the spicy noodle soup.
As we head back to
Cheongsapo station,
we caught a glimpse of
the Haeundae Blueline train
as it crosses the street.
It's a rather popular spot for photos
thanks to social media.
Instead of hopping back on the train to Mipo
we opted for the scenic route,
following the Moontan Road.
Moontan translates to "Moonlight Walk" and
is a trail where visitors can enjoy the
full glow of the moonlight as
they walk at night.
During the day however, you're provided
with views of the passing
sky capsules
and the ocean.
It's a very easy trail to do so I highly
recommend it if you're up for the walk.
We make our way to Haeundae Beach,
arguably the most famous
stretch of sand in Busan
We take a moment to soak in the beach
scenery and watch as the sun
sets over the horizon,
casting a golden glow over the area.
Before leaving,
we stop at the Tiger Gelatteok.
A place that serves rice cakes
filled with Italian gelato.
This gelato comes in a box with six
different flavors, perfect for a family,
but a bit much
just for the two of us.
No worries though,
we stash the extras in
our freezer for another time.
Here are more things to do in the area.
The next morning,
we head to the
Haedong Yonggungsa Temple,
also known as the Dragon Palace.
It's a stunning seaside Buddhist temple
perched on rocky cliffs right
above the sea.
What makes the temple unique is its rare
coastal location as most Korean
temples are located near mountains.
Next, we take the bus back,
heading towards
Gwangalli, but make a stop
at the Museum 1.
It's a media art museum
established in 2019.
Inside we find around
100 contemporary artworks,
from media installations
and video art
by 21 leading Korean and international
artists.
We make our way
back to Gwangalli Beach,
just in time to see the bridge light up.
If you happen to visit
Gwangalli on a weekend,
then keep an eye out for
the weekly drone show display
held every Saturday
at 8pm and 10pm.
It's a modern spectacle
against the night sky
adding a touch of magic
to the beach experience.
Here are a few more things
to do around the area.
For our final day in Busan, we head to
the Gamcheon Culture Village.
This colorful village is perched
on a steep hillside.
It's a vibrant splash of color and life,
which stands in stark contrast
to the bleak
past of the village.
Gamcheon was originally settled by war
refugees from across the country.
But in 2009, students, artists
and residents
decorated the village, transforming
the village
into what it is today.
We visit this cafe for some drinks, but
primarily for the panoramic
view of the village.
While exploring, we stumble upon
a photo flipbook store.
It's a quirky little shop where you can
create your own photo flipbook.
You'll find a selection of props you can use,
and the staff is incredibly helpful,
offering tips and guidance on
poses and what to do.
Not only does this make for a fantastic
souvenir, but it's also a unique
and fun experience
that I wholeheartedly recommend.
Afterwards, we make a stop at this
bakery for a quick snack.
Arguably the most famous spot
in the village,
the Stairs to See the Stars
is a steep 148-step staircase
It was used by villagers returning home
from the market who jokingly
proclaimed it was
so exhausting you'd see stars by the
time you reached the top.
We leave the village behind and
make our way to Seomyeon.
We start by exploring the
Jeonpo Cafe Street,
a paradise for cafe enthusiasts
with stylish
and aesthetic cafes on nearly
every corner.
Next, we decide to test our skills
and visited the Running Man
experience in Busan
It's an interactive game attraction
inspired by the popular Korean
variety show Running Man
Test yourself with a series of
games and challenges
straight out of the tv show,
and for those with
a competitive streak,
there's leaderboards to conquer
and various difficulty levels to tackle.
Initially, I thought it might be a bit
gimmicky, but it turned out to
be one of my favorite
experiences in Busan.
If you're a fan of the show, then this
is an absolute must-visit.
After burning off some calories, we were
starting to get hungry, so in
search for dinner, we
head down to the Pojangmacha Street.
You'll find rows of glowing orange tents serving
up Busan's boldest street food,
From spicy tteokbokki and grilled eel
to soju-fueled conversations with locals
this is where you get a glimpse
of the very soul of Busan.
Another gem, I want to mention is
Gijang Son Kalguksu
A popular no-frills
hole in the wall noodle shop.
where you can even witness the noodles
being hand pulled just right outside.
The star of the show
is their Son Kalguksu
thick, chewy noodles, swimming in a
rich, achovy based broth.
We finish the evening,
by exploring the lively Seomyeon.
For more things to do in Busan,
consider the following.
After ending our time in Busan,
we head to the airport
to catch a direct flight to Jeju Island.
Jeju Island is a place of raw, untamed
beauty with deep cultural roots.
It's a place where you can
get lost in the
breathtaking beauty of nature
and then reconnect
with the intricate weave of
local traditions.
Compared to Seoul and Busan,
this volcanic
island feels like stepping
into a different world.
A world that moves at its own pace.
We arrive at the airport and immediately
pick up a rental car.
We opted for an EV, the Hyundai IONIQ 5,
that served us well during
our Jeju adventures.
When renting a car in Jeju Island, there's
a couple of things to be aware of.
I highly recommend booking your car in advance
to lock in the cheaper rates.
Most cars come with built-in GPS with
integration with Naver Map.
Gas-driven cars are usually
much cheaper than
EVs, but if you decide to
go with an EV, then
you'll find plenty of charging
stations around
the island, and depending on
the rental company,
they might even provide you
with a charging card
that you could use to
charge your EV free of charge.
Driving on Jeju Island is relatively easy
compared to the major cities
such as Seoul
and Busan, but here are a couple of tips.
There are strict speed limits
on the island
with plenty of hidden speed
cameras, so be
sure to pay attention.
Right turns on red are allowed in Jeju
Island, which are something I
needed to get used to.
Traffic is generally light outside of Jeju City
which makes driving on the island
manageable even for beginners.
Overall, driving on Jeju Island is pretty
easy and straightforward.
It's also the best way to explore since
public transportation on the
island is limited.
We decided to stay in Jeju City and booked
a room at the Grand Hyatt Jeju.
This five-star hotel comes with all the
luxury amenities you'd expect.
A major plus for us was the EV charging
stations down at the parking
basement, which made it
easy for us to charge
our rental car overnight.
Depending on your room, you might even
catch a view of the airplanes
gliding in towards
the nearby airport.
We decide to head down to Dodu-dong,
The Rainbow Coastal Road.
It's a vibrant and colorful coastal road
known for its rainbow-colored wall
and ocean views.
Local residents had long expressed their
desire to liven out the plane protected
walls along the coastal road,
which was
initially installed
to prevent cars from
skidding off the edge.
What began as a safety measure
evolved
into a colorful landmark
of Jeju Island.
Not too far from Dodu-dong,
we stumble upon
a pair of red and white
horse-shaped lighthouses
standing proudly at the edge of a port.
Next, we head to the Abebe Bakery.
Here you'll find these cream-filled
donuts,
which comes in different flavors
and toppings.
Having difficulty in deciding
on what to get,
we end up buying a whole box,
saving the rest
for later.
In the evening, we made our
way to Dongmun Market.
Dongmun has been the heartbeat of Jeju's
local food scene since 1945,
and as soon as
you step inside, you'll understand why.
The narrow alleys are packed with vendors
enticing you with sizzling street food.
The smells are overwhelming in
the best way possible.
There's no escaping the pull of it.
It's also in the market where we find the
Young Handsome Men lobsters,
where eligible young bachelors
charm you with K-pop dance moves
while serving up grilled lobster.
Just your regular lobster
not anything special,
but I'm all there for the show.
The show was awesome
the guys showed a lot of showmanship,
5 out of 10 for the lobster
and 10 out of 10
for the showmanship.
Of course, after some food,
we're topping it off with some local
halabong tangerine juice
freshly extracted from
the shop right over here.
On our second day in Jeju,
we made our way
to the eastern side of the
island to visit
Seongsan Ilchulbong, also
known as Sunrise Peak.
It's a 5,000-year-old volcanic crater that
rises dramatically from the sea.
It's famous for its view of the sunrise, which
is why so many people wake up at an
ungodly hour to make the climb.
We didn't quite manage that, and honestly,
I  kinda wish we had.
And the hike to the summit? A short
incline of just 20 to 30 minutes.
We make our way down to meet the legendary
Inu Jeju's famous sea woman.
These incredible women have been diving with
breathing equipment for centuries,
harvesting seafood straight
from the ocean floor.
For these women, this isn't just
a job, it's a way of life.
There's a daily show that's
part singing and
part dancing, but don't expect
too much from it.
Afterward, the women dive
into the sea, and
you can actually buy whatever
they catch,
and have it prepared for you
at a nearby restaurant.
Next, we make a quick stop
at the Gwangchigi beach
known for its expansive
tidal flats,
black volcanic rocks, and the view
of Seongsan Ilchulbong.
During low tide, the beach reveals moss-covered
rocks and shallow tidal pools,
hosting small creatures like tiny crabs,
snails, and shellfish.
A need for some caffeine,
we stop by Cafe Orrrn.
This place has the kind of minimalist, sleek
design you'd expect to find in a
trendy city, not on the coast of
a volcanic island.
But that's the beauty of Jeju.
The cafe's sharp lines and
modern architecture
blends perfectly with the rugged
coastline outside,
a perfect stop after a morning
of hiking and exploring.
For a nearby optional activity,
Bunder Des Lumieres is a former
military bunker that has been turned
into a digital art museum.
Inside, you'll find high-definition
projections of famous artworks.
However, I would recommend spending your
time at the Snoopy Garden.
It's amusing in all the right ways, like
stepping into the mind of
Charles Schulz himself,
where Snoopy, Charlie Brown, and the rest
of the gang live out their endless,
existential crisis against a backdrop
of colorful exhibits.
The garden is beautifully themed, and the
whole atmosphere is surprisingly
charming.
I'll admit, I'm not the biggest Snoopy
fan, but even I found the
whole thing amusing.
So if you're a die-hard Snoopy fan, then
let me be blunt. You need to visit.
To finish the day, we make our
way to Seopjikoji.
Famous for featuring in several
Korean dramas,
it's a stunning stretch of coastline
where volcanic rock
formations meet the deep blue waters
of the East China Sea.
A highlight of the area is the lighthouse
that sits at the top of a hill.
Climbing up to it rewards you with an unbeatable
view of the nearby coastline.
On our third day in Jeju, we start
by visiting the Hueree Park.
Known for the season of flower
displays, visitors can
experience the varied flower
seasons of Jeju Island.
During autumn, you can expect to see
the Pink Muhly grass gardens.
While in spring, hydrangeas dominate
the landscape.
There's even a small pig farm
experience. It's
part of the mini animal farm
within the park.
Here you can interact with and
feed the black Jeju pigs.
It's time for some waterfalls.
The first to be the Jeongbang waterfall.
It's one of the few waterfalls
in the world,
where the water tumbles directly
into the sea.
Later we found ourselves at
the Cheonjiyeon waterfall
arguably the most famous
waterfall in Jeju Island.
Next, we visit the Oedolgae,
a volcanic sea stack rising about 20 meters
from the southern part of Jeju.
Its name literally means "lonely rock".
Next up is Gamttanam,
a tangerine-themed cafe and orchid.
The cafe sits beside a tangerine orchid
run by a family for generations.
During autumn and winter, you can
pick your own tangerines,
tools, baskets, and weighing included
At the small cafe, you can sip on house
favorites like the fresh halabong juice
and taste desserts, such as
the tangerine mousse cake.
For dinner, we decided to dine in
an order some room service.
We begin our final day in Jeju
by visiting the Arte Museum.
Arguably the most impressive digital art museum
I've come across during this trip.
The digital art displays are both unique
and visually impressive.
The museum features a variety
of exhibitions
that aims to transport you into
visually stunning realms.
We head to Saebil, a cafe housed in
an abandoned hotel resort.
It features a large interior space,
with plenty of seating,
and a large variety of big
goods and beverages.
The cafe also features an outdoor area,
which is full of pink muhly grass,
creating the perfect backdrop, awesome
photos, and detail.
We also make a quick stop
by the lonely tree,
not too far from the cafe.
We then head to the Osulloc Tea Museum,
a small museum dedicated to rich
history of Korean tea.
There's also a large outdoor space, which
features a beautiful green tea field.
Within the museum grounds, you can
find an innisfree store,
a well-known Korean skincarebrand.
There's also a cafe where
you can sample
Osulloc's various teas
and tea-flavored dessert.
And finally, we spend our remaining time
at the Sinchang Windmill Coastal Road
A scenic coastal path known for its stunning
coastal views and iconic windmills.
The coastal road is known for its
spectacular sunsets,
as the sun dips below the horizon,
the sky transforms
into a canvas of vibrant colors.
Many flock to the spot in the evening
to capture the stunning views.
We personally found it to be
the perfect way to end our time in Jeju.
If you want a more exciting or fun
way to finish your time in Jeju
Then consider spending
the day at 9.81 Park
Korea's first ever non-motorized
racing theme park,
that offer visitors the chance
to experience gravity racing,
which allows you to race in gokarts
with help of gravity
For more things to do in Jeju,
check out the following.
Before wrapping things up, let's quickly
break down the budget for this trip.
Our flights from Copenhagen to South Korea,
including domestic flights to and from
Jeju Island, came to around
1,925 US dollars.
Accommodation costs total of about 2,246 US
dollars, but this can be brought down
if you opt for more budget-friendly stays.
In total, the trip cost us approximately
5,521 US dollars for two people.
Alright, so that was how to spend
14 days in South Korea.
Yet again, if you want a written version
of all this, be sure to check out
my South Korea travel guide,
where I go into much more details
about the trip,
including activities, cafes, and restaurants
that didn't make it into this video.
It's designed to help you get the most out
of your time in South Korea, and if
you'd like to support me and
the channel directly,
grabbing a copy of the guide is
the best way to do it.
Overall, I had an incredible time
in South Korea,
and I hope this video inspires you to
take your very own trip.
This is Allan, safe travels out there,
and I'll see you guys soon.